# LUCINALDO DA COSTA

### Contact

+351 965 093 083 dacostalucinaldo@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/lucinaldo-costa https://github.com/lucinaldocosta (LC - Codes) https://bit.ly/3Am3sx3 Porto, Portugal

## **Summary**

Highly motivated and enthusiastic Full Stack Web Developer with over 2 years of experience in coding and building websites.

Proficient in transforming intricate layouts into modern designs with excellent usability, scalability, and accessibility.

Committed to continuous learning and personal growth.

### Education

### Harvard

2023 - 2023

# CS50 Introduction to Computer Science

C, JavaScript, Python, SQL, Flask, Data Structures, Algorithms.

### **Autodidact**

#### Developer

2021 - Current

HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS, Git, Github, Rest API, SQL, SQLite3, APIs, JSON, CRUD, Gimp.

# University Nove de Julho (UNINOVE)

Computer Science 2019/03 - 2020/06

### Maria Ana Sanz

Technician in 2016/09 - 2017/06
Microcomputer Systems
and Networks

### Skills

- HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript.
- · React.
- NodeJS, Rest API, CRUD.
- · Python, Flask
- · Git, Github.
- SQL, SQLite3, MySQL.
- Gimp, DaVinci Resolve.

## Work Experience

### Full Stack Web Developer

2023/05 - Current

CHAT WEB Freelancer

- Design and develop the interactive and visually appealing user interface of the web chat using modern front-end tecnologies.
- Implement the business logic and chat functionality on the back-end.
- Integrate external services, such as real-time notifications and user authentication.

### Front End Web Developer

2023/03 - 2023/05

DRINKSPORTALS Freelancer

- Maintained and update existing websites.
- Built responsive web design and cross browser compatibility.
- Integrate APIs and third party services.

### Front End Web Developer

2022/04 - 2022/09

EuforiaChick Freelancer

- Developed website content and layout.
- Integrated APIs and third party services.
- Developed high quality web pages with Javascript vanilla.
- Built responsive web design and cross browser compatibility

## Languages

	UNDERSTANDING	SPEAKING	WRITING
ENGLISH	В1	В1	В1
SPANISH	C2	C2	C1
PORTUGUESE	C2	C2	C1